tamilmp3corner.net 2011-11-25

# Privacy Policy and Disclaimer | Latest And Old Mp3 Songs Free Download

**Privacy Policy for tamilmp3corner.Net**

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email at support[@]tamilmp3corner.net

Please Contact Us through E-Mail (support[@]tamilmp3corner.net), if you feel that any Content including Videos on this blog are objectionable or violating your copyrights. The objectionable content shall be promptly removed from our blog within24 hours.

Because we don't maintain the files, we cannot fix broken links. If you find a broken link let us know and, if possible, we'll try to find a new link. THANKS TO www.google.com

At tamilmp3corner.net, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by tamilmp3corner.net and how it is used. 

**Log Files**  
Like many other Web sites, tamilmp3corner.net makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable. 

**Cookies and Web Beacons**   
tamilmp3corner.net does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser. 

**DoubleClick DART Cookie**   
.:: Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on tamilmp3corner.net  
.:: Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to tamilmp3corner.net and other sites on the Internet.   
.:: Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL - http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html 

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include ....  
Google Adsense

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on tamilmp3corner.net send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see. 

tamilmp3corner.net has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers. 

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. tamilmp3corner.net's privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites. 

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers' respective websites.

## Terms of Use

The purpose of our site is not to enable you to download music you would otherwise purchase; instead, this site's purpose is to allow you, the user, to sample the music first in the comfort of your home and help you decide on what you want to purchase next time at the music store or at an online music store.  
This Site has been created in appreciation of Indian Music only and without any commercial motive. Any other files you download from this site, you agree to download at your own risk, and any bad effects of that on your computer is not our responsibility, its your responsibilty.   
By downloading any files from this site, you adhere to the rule above.  
The songs are NOT in any way meant to replace the actual soundtracks of the album. If you like what you hear, be sure to purchase the original cassette or CD.   
In no way, the author of this Archive or the page coder is promoting any movie, song or anything else mentioned on this site. The songs are meant for promotional purposes only and their sole copyright rests with their respective Audio Music Company.   
You may not download the songs, reproduce the songs in any way that results in copyright violation. We are not aware of any possible copyright violations. If any such act is brought to our attention we will remove the concerned songs from the website promptly.   
Certain links on the site lead to resources located on servers maintained by third parties over whom we have no control. We accept no responsibility or liability for any of the material contained on those servers and for any effects they have on your system. In no case the audio companies, legal owners, copyright owners etc. take this site or its owner or its publisher or its web-master to legal actions or court or else.   
If you disagree with the policies of this site, please terminate your connection now! 

**DISCLAIMER**

* All the Song links provided on this blog are taken from third party websites and blogs. We are in no way responsible for the quality or copyright issues that pertain to the downloads as we do not host anything and in fact, we act merely as a guide to the best resources[](http://tamilmp3corner.blogspot.com/2009/07/post-edit.g?blogID=4599064062214867895&postID=5259076955027025145) on the web. The downloaded material is intended for Preview and Testing purposes only. All the rights are reserved to the respective owners of the copyrighted material. All the users should delete the downloaded material within 24 hours and are highly encouraged to purchase the copyrighted material from the nearest shops selling them.
